He can go in, see? The kitten can go in.
Mira! Él puede entrar. El gatito consegue entrar.
Look.
Mira:
"For sale."
A la venta.
It's all for sale.
Todo para la venta.
"For sale". The whole street is for sale.
Para la venta. Toda la calle está a la venta.
All of a sudden.
De repente.
It's impressive. In 2013, the last eviction happened,
Es increíble. 2013 fue la ultima expulsión
a real state market boom happend on the surroundings.
Hubo un boom inmobiliario en los alrededores.
Look at this: the building has been put up at an incredible speed
Si nota aquí es lo siguiente:Este edificio aquí se elevó a una velocidad asombrosa
And it's not the only one. There are many of them.
Pero no es el único, hay muchos.
So, like, this used to be a car wash... so someone bought
Así que esa cosa. Compró una tierra barata, aquí era un lugar para lavar el auto,
a cheap lot just waiting for things to flourish.
esperando a que la cosa ande.
When the population that lived here is evicted,
Así que en el momento en que expropia y que la población de aquí es retirada
the lot becomes a prime area, "oh! there will be a cultural center!"
la tierra ya se valora:"¡Uy! surgirá un centro cultural! "
So they put up buildings.
Y ya sube emprendimiento.
You can see many signs of "for sale" there,
Allí hay varias tarjetas de venta.
which means prices have duplicated, triplicated
Es decir, los precios se duplifican, triplifican
on account of having a cultural center nearby.
a causa de que haya un centro cultural en el barrio.